PERSONAL DETAILS

Name : NGUYEN THAI THINH

Home Address : 254/10/6 TTH07 Street, Tan Thoi Hiep Ward, District 12, HCM City.

Hand phone : 0983 261 049

Personal Email : nguyenthaithinhit@gmail.com

Gender : Male

Marital status : Married

EDUCATION					
Year start	Year end	Degree	Specialization	University name	Rate
2001	2004	Bachelor of College	Information	Industrial College N.4	Good
		_	Technology	(University of Industry)	
2005	2005	CCNA Certification	Network	Nhat Nghe Training	Good
			Administrator	Center Network	
2006	2009	Bachelor of	Information Systems	University of Natural	Good
		University		Sciences HCM City	

CAREER SUMMARY

More than 6 years of experience in automation testing.

January 2015 to Present: Silver Spring Network Company

Tester and Developer

August 2008 to 2014: Vietbando Company

Developer

September 2004 to July 2008: Dolsoft, Vigiland Video Company

Tester and Developer

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

January 2015 to Present: Silver Spring Network Company

Tester and Developer

Duties

Project name: Detectent website

• Coding to create the automation scripts to test Detectent website.

- Platform: Visual Studio 2015, Visual Studio 2017, Visual Studio 2019, MSSQL 2008, MSSQL 2012, MySQL, Javascript.
- Research and apply new technologies for working.
 - 1. Selenium with programing language C#.
 - 2. Sikuli tool.
 - 3. CSS selector, XPath.
 - 4. MSTest, MbUnit, Gallio nUnit, TestStack White, NUnit.
 - 5. Jira.
 - 6. Mailtrap.
 - 7. AutoIt tool.

August 2008 to 2014:

Vietbando Company

Developer

Duties

Project name: Vietbando and Tusachtruongbacan website

- Coding to create module product page of Vietbando.
- Coding to create module Admin page of Vietbando.
- Coding to create module report and export to pdf, excel file of vietbando.
- Coding to create FTP and manage tool for Bus Tracking project.
- Coding to create services (window and web service) of vietbando.
- Coding to create module vietbando store.
- Coding to create project tusachtruongbacan website.

Desc

- Platform: Visual Studio 2005, Visual Studio 2008, Visual Studio 2010, MSSQL 2000, MSSQL 2005, MSSQL 2008, windows, MySQL, Javascript, jquery.
- Research and apply new technologies for working.
 - 8. Technologies WCF, WPF, MVC
 - 9. DotnetNuke open source.
 - 10. Mongo DB none SQL.
 - 11. Video Stream
 - 12. Membership in ASP.NET

September 2004 to July 2008:

Dolsoft, Vigiland Video Company

Tester and Developer

Duties

Project name: Cardetector, CamSmartz, LineUp

With team leader role, I worked jobs as below:

- Create test plan for projects as above.
- Create test cases for projects as above.
- Organized, breakdown and divided task to team member.
- Implement test cases.
- Post bug to bug tracker system.
- Create scripts to execute automated test cases.
- Using QTP for developing automation testing.
- Create test report to manage about result testing.

- Implement and keep system operation for Vietnam office, including following main services:
 - 1. Internet connection
 - 2. FTP, DNS, DHCP, PROXY...
 - 3. Web server (apache)
 - 4. Source Control (svn subversion)
 - 5. Bug tracker
- Research new features for Work
 - 13. Mongo DB.
 - 14. Video Stream

LANGUAGE SKILLS

+ English: level B (Good at writing, speaking, reading and listening.)

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Operating Systems

• Windows, Linux.

Database

- SQL Server
- MySQL
- Mongo DB

Network Communication

- Socket, UDP, TCP/IP, Web Services, HTTP.
- SNMP, SMTP, POP3.
- MCSA Network

Languages

- C#, ASP.Net, Jquery, JSP, Java
- Javascript, vbscript

Web

• ASP.net, PHP, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap.

Software Tools & Applications

- Email, ftp, web
- Bug tracker System
- Visual Source Safe
- GIT
- SVN

SALARY

Expected salary: Negotiable